Mother, you must help me.
Don't worry.
I will figure something out for you.
Master,
look at this.
We've raised a troublemaker.
It's infuriating.
I just couldn't stand seeing
Xue Ruowan marry into the General's Manor,
so I set a fire
in Ning Yuanci's residence.
Did you really set the fire
at the General's Manor?
Yes,
and I ran away right after.
Ning Yuanci is so heartless.
He actually used me as his spy.
And that Xue Ruowan...
She thinks marrying Ning Yuanci
is such a big
deal.
What a despicable couple.
You even dared to set a fire.
Are you going to
kill someone next?
So what if I do?
I'll kill whoever Father tells me to.
Stop talking nonsense.
Walls have ears.
I will handle this.
Just say
you went to your grandfather's to recover.
Ning Yuanci is already suspicious of you.
You must be careful.
I know, Father.
By the way, Father,
my painting and calligraphy theater
is almost ready.
When it opens,
bring some people to support me.
You are a lady of noble birth.
How can you
show your face in public so easily?
You like painting and calligraphy.
You can exchange ideas
with enthusiasts there.
Besides,
there are many people in the theater.
It's convenient for networking,
which will also help
your career, Father.
Watch me drug you
with a magic potion.
Lady Keying,
I finally get to see you.
Chu Qingjun,
are you alright?
I haven't seen you for days.
I've been worried about you.
Why did you come to the Duke's Residence?
Do you know
how dangerous it is here?
Ning Yuanci kindly let you out.
You should hurry home and stay there.
I haven't seen you for days,
but my mind
is filled with your image.
Lady Keying,
love arises unexpectedly
and runs deep.
My feelings for you
are genuine.
Forget about Ning Yuanci.
Don't
misuse your devoted male lead
persona.
If Chu Qingyun really falls for me
and ruins the plot,
I'm doomed.
If the old fox finds out
Ning Yuanci let Chu Qingyun go,
he might get suspicious.
For a scholar like you,
Ning Yuanci letting you go
means he thinks you're worthless.
Let me tell you,
there's no position for you
in the Duke's estate either.
Get out.
Ying'er.
I invited Mr. Chu here.
Mr. Chu remained unyielding
even under Ning Yuanci's
severe torture.
I invited him today
to help you
run the entertainment house well.
He is very talented.
I admire him a lot.
Thank you for giving me
a new life, Your Grace.
I
will definitely do my best to help.
What?
What is that old fox
up to?
I advise you not to waste your time
on me.
This is not something you should be doing.
Ning Yuanci isn't the only one
in this world
who can protect you.
I can do it too.
I like things I earn
through my own efforts.
I don't like those
who throw themselves at me.
Can you do something useful
with your time?
You can't even tell friend from foe.
What am I going to do with you?
Although I don't have
the power and influence of Ning Yuanci...
Trust me.
I will work hard
to be a man worthy
of you.
If the relationships
keep getting this messy,
I won't know
how to end this.
Does your heart ache for him?
Why are you here?
Aren't you afraid
the old fox will see you?
How does it feel to be pestered
by a man?
Are you jealous?
Me, jealous?
He doesn't deserve it.
As expected,
you were lying when you said you cared.
Are you crying?
No.
Hearing him say he likes you,
of course I'd be jealous.
I wish I could stab him twice.
Stop crying.
I was wrong.
Don't forget,
I can cry
or laugh whenever I want.
You just love acting to trick me,
don't you?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Are you mad?
I was tricking you too.
How dare you, Ning Yuanci!
Once the theater opens,
Xue Shiyan
will probably use this place
to pass on intelligence.
We need to be more careful
with our actions
from now on.
We can't let them find out
we're conspiring together.
What are you thinking about?
Did Chu Qingyun take the initiative
to show goodwill to Xue Shiyan
just to get close to you?
Can you stop thinking
like a jealous lover?
It must be Xue Shiyan's scheme.
I have to keep a close eye on him.
Besides, based on what I know about
Chu Qingyun,
he wouldn't
help Xue Shiyan do bad things.
You know him very well.
Even if Chu Qingyun
deliberately tries to get close to you,
you're not allowed to talk to him.
Did you hear me?
You're a married man.
What right do you have
to tell me what men I can see?
Your sister has already accepted
the divorce letter I wrote her.
I can announce it to the world at any time
and then marry you.
Who said I'm going to marry you?
Besides,
a happy ending
doesn't have to end in marriage.
My primary task is
to protect Xue Ruowan
and help her gain freedom and happiness.
As for you,
go avenge
your family and friends.
Then move on from the past
and welcome a new life.
When everything is over,
are you
going back to your own world?
If I fail,
I won't be able to go back.
I might even disappear completely.
Who knows who I'll become
in the next reincarnation.
You might not even recognize me.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
I won't let you disappear.
At first,
I thought I kept failing
because I didn't understand
this world.
Later I realized that
even if I followed the rules,
this world still wouldn't
run according to my will.
So,
I've decided.
From now on,
I'm going to follow my heart
and be myself to the fullest.
Although the ending
might not be rewritten,
the choice of
how each chapter is presented
is in our hands.
We need to fully
immerse ourselves in the moment.
And act it out
to the fullest.
No matter what the ending is,
I'll stay with you till the end.
Congratulations!
Wishing you a prosperous business!
Welcome.
Come, let's go inside.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Welcome.
Congratulations. Thank you.
Please take a seat inside.
Let's go inside.
Come on in.
Welcome.
Come, have a seat inside.
Father, you're here.
Let's go.
This way, please.
Please come in.
Sit down.
Please, sit.
What do you think?
This is my theater.
Not bad.
Why are you here?
I don't recall inviting you.
Have you forgotten, Sister?
I also poured my heart
into this theater.
Wan'er,
it's good that you still care
about your family.
My wife has been unwell since
she was frightened
by the fire on our wedding night.
I insisted she
stay in the residence to rest.
Father-in-law, please understand.
Last time I rushed over
to demand her back,
it was out of concern.
General,
please don't mind it.
Useless people
are just so dramatic.
She is truly valiant.
Your performance of Mulan joining the army
is truly spectacular, Sister.
Look,
every move she makes
truly has the bearing of a female general.
Ying'er was spoiled since childhood,
yet she has grown much more sensible now.
and are willing to share my burdens.
Seeing a woman don armor
and bravely kill enemies,
My Lord Duke, did it not remind you
of your own military years?